databasedev.co.uk 2013-08-05

# Printing Query Parameter Values in your Report | Database Solutions for Microsoft Access | databasedev.co.uk

**Privacy**

We take our users rights to privacy and security when online very seriously and will only hold personal information that fully complies with Data Protection legislation. 

Our Privacy Policy goes along way to ensure your privacy and explains how we collect information about you, how we use this information and how we will ensure that your information stays secure.

By using this web site you consent to us collecting and using your personal information on the terms set out in this Privacy Policy.

We reserve the right to change the terms of the Privacy Policy from time to time, so please re-visit here now and again.

**How do we collect information about site visitors?**

This web site may request you to enter personal details when registering with certain areas of the site. Of these details we may collect your name, postal and email address, which pages you visit and how often. Sometimes you may be asked for personal information, mainly when contacting us by e-mail or completing any on-line forms.

**How do we use the information we collect?**

We will not send you any unwanted junk mail, however occasionally we may send you details of new features or services relating to our type of business. Information will also be used to help us improve the site and inform you of any offers, products or services that we think may interest you.

**Do we pass the information we collect onto third parties?**

All information is held privately and is not passed on to any other party. We will not sell or rent members lists to any other party. You should be aware that if the police or any other regulatory authority investigating illegal activities, requests that we provide your personal details or information concerning your activities whilst visiting the site, we shall do so.

**How secure is the personal information we collect?**

Keeping your information secure is of prime importance to us, therefore we assure you that we will use all measures to safeguard your personal data. Although we make every effort to create a secure environment for your information, we cannot guarantee that the personal information you transmit to us online will be 100% safe. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on databasedev.co.uk to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
